msdesignbd.com 2017-12-30

# Privacy Policy - MS Design | Free Blogger Templates 2017

####  Privacy Policy for MS Design

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [Contact Page](http://www.msdesignbd.com/p/contact.html).

At msdesignbd.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by msdesignbd.com and how we use it.

###  Log Files

Like many other Web sites, msdesignbd.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

###  Cookies and Web Beacons

msdesignbd.com uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

###  Third Party Privacy Policies

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. msdesignbd.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

###  Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

###  Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, July 3rd, 2015.

Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
